It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's a family guy
We now return to
Rodney King of Queens.
Rodney, did you take out the trash?
I forgot.
Oh, no, she didn't.
Pizza for Adam West.
No! You gave me Canadian bacon
instead of bacon!
This misdeed cannot go unpunished.
Pizza delivery man,
prepare to meet your maker
at the hands of my cat-launcher.
Hey, look! Somebody tried to break into
the dirty-movie store.
Quick! Grab as many as you can
before someone sees us.
Damn, I lost him.
All right cats, back in the bag.
Come on, Fluffy.
Come on, Mittens.
Come on, Paul.
What a ridiculous name for a cat.
Paul. That's a person's name!
A person's name.
Oh, Paul.
Oh, man, this is gonna be great.
Oh, are we watching a movie?
The lab results are back.
You've tested positive for nymphomania.
Oh, no! What should I do?
Take two of these
and call us in the morning.
Well, now that's not going to help
her nymphomania,
it's only going to exacerbate it.
Oh, my God, what are you kids doing?
Out! Everybody out!
Oh!
Oh! That's bogus.
Chris, what is this?
Genital Hospital.
Yes, and it's inappropriate
for someone your age.
Now, if you're curious about sex,
you should talk to your Sex Ed teacher.
We don't have one.
The principal cut Sex Ed class
to save money.
What? Well, that's crazy!
Without Sex Ed,
kids can wind up sexually confused.
Just look at Michael Jackson.
The kid in me likes the frosted side.
But the grown-up in me
likes the kid in me.
Peter, do you know they're not teaching
Sex Ed at Chris' school?
Let him figure it out the way I had to,
with a can of Crisco and a shot glass.
That's the natural way, Lois.
That's the natural way.
Well, somebody's got to step in.
Tomorrow,
I'm going down to James Woods High
and offer to teach the class myself.
Hey, you could really make a difference.
Like I did when I taught
money management to those drug addicts.
There's a lot of ways for you guys
to save money.
For example, you're all shooting up.
Why not share needles?
That's a no-brainer.
More money in your wallet,
more drugs in your veins.
My second piece of advice,
have as many kids as you can,
'cause that makes it more likely
that one of those kids will grow up
and make it big in Hollywood.
Then who's paying the bills, huh?
Hollywood kid.
Class dismissed.
Good morning, everyone!
I'm Mrs. Griffin, your new Sex Ed teacher.
Now, you've probably heard
all those rumors
that condoms make sex less pleasurable.
While that is a fact,
they also make sex safer.
Sorry I'm late, Lois.
Peter, what are you doing here?
Lois, you think I'm going to miss a chance
to share my knowledge
with these fresh, young minds? Forget it.
I've missed too many other opportunities.
- There he is.
- Took you long enough.
Just what we need.
Hey, guys, I'm coming in.
- Oh, no!
Oh, God!
Oh, boy!
I am not going to hear the end of this.
- You jackass!
- Now you've done it!
Idiot!
I know I don't fit here,
but I'm just gonna settle right in.
All right, Peter, you can stay,
but remember, this is my class.
Now, there are a number of natural ways
that males and females interact.
That's right! Allow me to demonstrate.
Hey, Rainbow Brite.
Hello, Shakespeare.
I am all done writing plays for the day.
Perhaps we could have sexual intercourse.
Count me in!
I say, look at this.
This toy has small parts.
Why the devil would they include
small parts?
Unless, I'm supposed to eat them.
Of course, it all adds up.
Oh, dear God, I've lost a tooth.
Dude, you're lucky.
If you put that under your pillow,
the tooth fairy'll come
and give you a dollar.
What?
Did you say the tooth fairy comes here?
To our house?
She just breaks in like some hood?
Yeah, she creeps into your house at night
and comes into your room
while you sleep.
- Oh, my God!
- And sometimes, just for the hell of it,
she cuts off a piece of her armpit hair
and places it gently on your tongue.
Oh, God! Oh, God! I got to get out of here!
I got to get out of here!
Stewie, calm down. Get a hold of yourself.
Here, Brian, let me handle this.
Calm down,
everything's gonna be all right.
Chris, you're wanted on the phone.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Hey, Lois, I wanted to get some K-Y jelly
for the class today,
but they were all out, so I got Smucker's.
Peter, I don't know what you think
you're doing,
but you've ruined my Sex Ed class.
There's no way you're coming
with me again.
Fine, but without my advice,
those kids are gonna be as hopeless
as Liam Neeson
when he tries to play
an American cowboy.
But, Montana, when will you be back?
That's none of your concern.
You gotta take care of the offspring.
Gonna take a fortnight at least
to get this herd down
to St. Louis on Mississippi.
This glen's gonna be tough to traverse.
And that river's gotta be
50, 60 meters wide,
and God knows how many fathoms.
To hell with parliamentary procedure.
We've got to wrangle up some cattles.
What is going on here?
We're all protesting the Sex Ed class
that's being taught to our children.
Mrs. Griffin,
I'm sorry to have to tell you this,
but the school board has voted
to cancel your Sex Ed class.
Look, Principal Shepherd,
I know my husband acted inappropriately.
Oh, it's not because of your husband.
It's because you're teaching those kids
about condoms.
What? That's ridiculous.
These students have the right
to information about safe sex.
Well, these parents don't think so.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Griffin, you're fired.
Fired! Oh, no!
I can't believe they fired you.
Can't you go down to the school
and try to reason with them?
No, I'm banned from school property.
The PTA doesn't want me
around their children.
Well, Lois, I think you did the right thing
by trying to inform these kids
about safe sex,
and if the parents don't like it,
that's their loss.
That's the problem, though,
it isn't their loss, it's the kids' loss.
I just hope they're getting
the information they need.
All right, students,
we have a special speaker today
who's going to educate you about sex.
Please welcome
from the First Evangelical Church,
the Reverend Jerry Kirkwood
and the Opal Ring Crusade.
Hey, kids, put your Walkmans down
and listen up,
because we're gonna talk about sex.
Sex? Hang on there, Jerry.
God, what are you doing here?
I was just passing through on my way
to see The Matrix.
- We can relate to that.
- No fake.
Well, God,
I am here to talk to these kids about sex.
Uh-oh.
- And why they shouldn't be having it.
- That is boss.
Hey, you kids like MADtv?
Well, we've got something
almost as good.
Here they are, the Opal Ring Players.
Boy, I sure had fun
at the pizza parlor tonight, Debbie.
Yeah, Matthew,
that pizza pie was delicious.
Hey, watch out, crazy driver.
That joker must have been
from Jefferson High.
They're our rivals.
Well, here we are at the make out point.
- Yeah, you wanna go all the way?
- Freeze!
Now, who can tell me
what Matthew just did wrong?
I mean, besides not running over
that yahoo from Jefferson High.
They're our rivals.
He's wrong because he wants to have sex,
and he's not married.
Bingo!
- Wow, you're pretty smart.
- Thanks. My name's Doug.
I'm Meg.
Now, look, let's rap for a second.
He's sitting informally like us.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Jefferson High is our rival.
Sure, sex is fun, but you can't have it
before you're married.
Even if you use a condom.
Because not only do condoms fail
100 percent of the time,
they're also majorly unsafe.
Hey, you wouldn't put a plastic bag
over your grandmother's head would you?
No.
And that's why we're gonna be
handing out these opal rings.
These rings are a symbol
of your commitment
to refrain from sex until you're married.
So, what do you say?
Who wants to be joyful?
Who wants to be pure?
Who wants to be abstinent?
- Wow, he makes so much sense.
- I know, he's a visionary.
Like Gandhi or Mozart or Picasso.
Ladies and gentlemen, my newest work.
Now, I know this person
looks a little mixed-up,
but watch carefully.
If I move this down here,
and this over here.
And this part here.
Anyone tell who it is yet? No?
Okay, well, what if I move this here,
and this here.
And it's Dianne Wiest.
All right, men, your mission tonight
is to stave off the invading forces
of the tooth fairy.
SpongeBob, you watch the east.
Starscream, you take the west.
And Man-E-Faces, you take center patrol
since you have many faces.
What... What...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, it's okay. It's morning.
Is it? I knew it, I scared her off.
You might wanna check under your pillow.
How did she get in?
She must have been quieter than
Britney Spears' dietician.
Easy on those trans-fats.
Not everything needs gravy.
You know, there're some carrots
down at the other end.
That cheesecake was for everyone.
Her hand was right beneath my pillow.
She could have snapped my neck
if she had a mind to.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure it will be a while
before you lose another tooth.
I can't wait for that.
I have to lure her back on my terms
and kill her myself.
But to catch a fairy,
I have to think like a fairy.
If you want Brian to say,
'"Well that'll be a stretch, '"
text message FAMGUY1.
If you want Brian to say,
'"I'm not touching that one, '"
text FAMGUY2.
If you want Brian to say, "Arriba,"
and dance around a sombrero,
text FAMGUY3.
Enter now.
Thanks for voting.
Arriba!
We now return
to Laguna Beach.
- Like, right?
- I know.
- Whatever, because...
- I know, right?
Whatever, because, I mean, like,
totally full-out.
- Full-on.
- Right?
I guess it's not easy growing up anywhere.
Hey, Dad! Check out my abstinence ring.
It means I made a pledge not to have sex.
That's crazy! You can't give up sex.
You've got a responsibility.
You see, Meg.
You're what they call a practice girl.
Dad, look at the facts about sex.
"If you have sex, your penis will fall off
and land in another dimension
"populated entirely by dogs
who will eat it. "
Well, that's something I'd like to avoid.
Well, this changes everything.
From now on, I, too, will be abstinent.
I'll be as untouched as the turn signal
in an Asian woman's car.
How much signal I need
to cut across eight lane?
None? I turn now.
Good luck, everybody else.
All right, getting a tooth
to lure that damn fairy back
shouldn't be too difficult.
I'd love to dance, Fred Savage.
Set, hut...
Gosh, Meg, I really wish we could take
our relationship to the next level.
I know. I feel the same way,
but we made a decision to be abstinent.
Of course,
there are ways we can keep our pledge
- and still do other things.
- You're right.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Oh, there it is. I see it.
You know, Roy, I hope you play squash
better than you pass.
Well, we'll find out this Saturday.
All right, Peter,
you ready for role-playing night?
Here comes Grimace,
"You got some burgers I can steal?"
Lois, the Hamburglar steals burgers,
Grimace is Ronald MacDonald's
retarded friend.
Oh, come on,
you love the dirty-talking Grimace. You...
- Peter, what the hell is this?
- My chastity belt.
A chastity belt?
What in God's name is that for?
I'm abstinent, Lois.
It's all in these pamphlets
Meg brought home from school.
Sex turns straight people gay
and turns gays into Mexicans.
Everyone goes down a notch.
This is nonsense.
You can't force abstinence on kids.
Lois, what possible harm
can abstinence do?
Meg Griffin, we need to have a talk.
Mom!
Oh, my God!
You kids were doing it in the ear!
Hey, my sandwich tastes funny.
Is there something wrong
with the Smucker's?
Yeah, it's been on my penis.
Meg, I still cannot believe what you
and Doug did last night.
Mom, you don't understand.
Doug and I are abstinent.
But if we have sex in the ear,
it doesn't count.
We're still pure in the eyes of the Lord.
Meg, when I was your age,
my parents tried to feed me
the same nonsense about premarital sex.
- You're lying to yourself.
- Well, I don't care what you think.
Doug and I are part of the
Opal Ring Crusade,
and this is how we choose
to express our love.
Look, Meg.
A, ear sex is just unnatural
and B...
How do I say this?
Vaginal intercourse is...
It's just tops.
It's the bee's knees, Meg.
Oh, when you rattle it around just right.
Oh, my God! I mean...
You remember, when we had that old car
with the bad shocks,
and I used to take the old dirt road
on purpose?
Meg... Meg?
I love you.
In local news, a sexy new trend
has emerged at James Woods High.
That's right, Tom.
It appears that students
have taken to having ear sex
in lieu of traditional intercourse.
Over 200 reports of ear sex
have been confirmed so far,
prompting a new slogan,
'"Once you go black, you go deaf. '"
Sounds like there's
a pattern developing, Tom.
Oh, a pattern developing?
Well, Diane, I guess you've learned a lot
from staring lifelessly
at TVreruns of CSI over
the thrusting shoulders of whatever drifter
you drag into your bedroom
on whatever night CSI is on.
- Thursdays, Tom.
- And don't miss CSI, Thursday
when Johnny Cluestein
finds the secret fingerprints
in the case... I've never seen the show.
Brian, I'll be right back.
- I'm gonna use the little girls' room.
- All right, baby.
An entire week and still no teeth.
And it turns out these teeth
I got from the old man are phony.
Brian... Brian, look, I'm Gary Busey.
I'm frequently aggressive
in situations that don't call for it.
What the hell is that?
That's Jillian. She's...
She... She has this eating disorder.
- She's bulimic.
- My God! That's horrible.
I know, it really is.
I mean, her hair is falling out.
- Last week, she lost a tooth.
- Really?
But man, I'll tell you, all that purging
just makes her body look fantastic.
I mean, that's what the supermodels do,
and so many of them just look so great.
Karen Carpenter overdid it,
but I think Jillian's found a good balance.
I'm really surprised
you invited me out for dinner, Stevie.
Oh, well, you know,
I just wanted to touch base, see how...
It's Stewie, by the way.
Just to check in, make sure everything's
going well with you and Brian.
It's going kick-ass!
Well, you look fantastic.
Lots of meat on your bones.
- Which is great.
- What?
Oh, just saying you look jolly.
Like Ruben Studdard
- or John Goodman or Santa.
- Oh, my God!
Are you saying I'm fat?
No, I'm saying Santa's thin...
- Get in there and throw up!
- Oh!
Excellent!
Now, I'm prepared to fight the tooth fairy.
Just like Geri fought comedy
on The Facts of Life.
Hey, Blair did you find a purse at the mall?
Actually, I found seven.
One for every day of the week.
I'm wide awake, Peter.
- You wanna mess around?
Lois, you know I'm abstinent.
Come on, can't you break
your stupid pledge for one night?
Well, I guess
we do both have needs.
Oh, Peter.
Peter, what... What are you doing?
What the... What the hell...
What are you doing? Peter!
What the hell is wrong with you?
This is all I can do, Lois. I'm abstinent.
That is it.
I am gonna have regular sex with you
whether you like it or not.
- No!
- I wasn't asking your permission.
No, no. No, I'm abstinent!
This is an affront to the Lord. No!
No!
Oh, I see what you're driving at.
Oh, that was fantastic.
Hey, when'd you get that tattoo
on your lower back?
I don't know, Peter,
meth is a hell of a drug.
- What?
- I'm just glad to have you back on my side.
I only wish I could convince Meg
and her classmates, too.
We'll show them somehow, Lois.
I'll be more convincing than Mel Gibson
when he apologized to the Jews.
I'm really, really sorry
about your big noses.
I'm really sorry about how greedy you are.
But most of all,
I'm really sorry about your dirty,
underhanded, back-stabbing ways.
Your number one,
dirty Jew fan, Mel Gibson.
All right, tooth whore, do your worst.
A- ha!
Stewie, what the hell?
Get me down from here.
No way, man! How do I know you're not
the tooth fairy in disguise?
- Your middle name is Gilligan.
- Not good enough.
- You think my girlfriend's a moron.
- So does everyone.
You have a picture of Chris Noth
in your wallet.
Okay.
Look, Stewie, this is ridiculous.
There's something I have to tell you.
- The tooth fairy isn't real.
- What?
Look, I didn't wanna burst your bubble
since you're just a kid,
but, yeah, she's all smoke and mirrors.
Just like Harry Houdini.
I don't wanna play bridge
with the Petersons tonight.
Harry, we agreed weeks ago
and we're going.
All right, fine. Let me get my coat.
Oh, wait a second!
Damn it, I am not going by myself.
Ah, you bitch.
Very well then,
I suppose that bile-spewing skirt of yours
can have her tooth back.
- What... It's gone!
- Whoa! I wonder what happened to it.
Fuck, yeah!
Peter, how are we
gonna get past the guard?
Lois, I think I just got an idea.
You see that guy with the overcoat?
He's tall enough for us to sneak in
behind him, come on.
So remember, sex is bad,
immoral, and wrong.
And if you have sex,
you're automatically in Al-Qaeda.
Kids, do not listen to this man.
He is wrong. He is feeding you lies.
Now look, it's true you shouldn't have sex
until you're ready.
You should wait until you're in love.
But, I mean, hey, we're all human, huh?
We have urges
and they are perfectly natural.
And if you do make the choice
to act on them,
make sure you protect yourselves.
Use a condom.
- I'm gonna use condoms.
- Me, too.
Maybe, I'll use two condoms
at the same time.
- Why would you do that?
- Oh, I mean, just one, just one.
Doug, my mom's right.
If we really care about each other,
it's okay to have sex.
We'll be safe, we'll use a condom,
and it'll be wonderful.
Wow, does this mean I'll see you naked?
- Yeah.
- Oh, boy, I can't wait.
- I'm sorry Doug dumped you, honey.
- It's all your fault.
I'm proud of you, sweetheart.
Me, too, Lois,
you stood up for what you believe in.
I just wish I could have been there
to hear the speech you made.
You think you could give me a little taste?
If you want to
hear Lois' speech,
text message FAMGUY1.
If you wanna hear Meg talk about her day,
text FAMGUY2.
If you wanna give Cleveland
his first line of the episode,
text FAMGUY3.
Enter now.
Thanks for voting.
Hey, ya'll, sock it to me.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru